Hi, I'm Chris Murray, and I'm going to show you how to warm up using touch drills.
In soccer, it's very important for you to warm up with and without the ball.
By warming up without the ball allows you to get your muscles warm enough and be able to stretch.
By warming up with the ball really gets you a feel for the ball and gets you ready to play.
Some little touch drills that you can do to warm up are extremely simple.
One touch drill that you can do to warm up is just boxes on the ball.
Boxes on the ball are done by having the ball in between your feet and touching the ball back and forth.
This really allows for you to get your legs warm and for you to get a feel for the ball.
Another touch drill that you can do to warm up for soccer is touches on top of the ball.
Touches on top of the ball are done by just jogging in place, touching the top of the ball with the soles of your feet.
This is another way to really get your legs warm for a soccer game.
Another touch drill to do before a soccer game is just simple dribbling.
By dribbling around in a large area or even in a small area really allows you to get a feel for the ball.
And those are just some touch drills to do when you warm up for soccer.